 export const games = [
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Who%20is%20the%20main%20antagonist%20in%20the%20Portal%20franchise%3F",
     correct_answer: "GLaDOS",
     incorrect_answers: ["Chell", "Wheatley", "Rick"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20cancelled%20sequel%20of%20Team%20Fortress%3F",
     correct_answer: "Team%20Fortress%202%3A%20Brotherhood%20of%20Arms",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Team%20Fortress%202%3A%20Desert%20Mercenaries",
       "Team%20Fortress%202%3A%20Operation%20Gear%20Grinder",
       "Team%20Fortress%202%3A%20Return%20to%20Classic",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20game%20did%20NOT%20get%20financed%20via%20Crowdfunding%3F",
     correct_answer: "Enter%20the%20Gungeon",
     incorrect_answers: ["Town%20of%20Salem", "Undertale", "Tower%20Unite"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20Kingdom%20Hearts%2C%20how%20many%20members%20does%20Organization%20XIII%20have%20in%20total%3F",
     correct_answer: "14",
     incorrect_answers: ["10", "13", "12"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Blinky%2C%20Pinky%2C%20Inky%20and%20Clyde%20are%20characters%20from%20which%20classic%20video%20game%3F",
     correct_answer: "Pac-Man",
     incorrect_answers: ["Gauntlet", "Space%20Invaders", "Street%20Fighter"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20these%20video%20game%20engines%20was%20made%20by%20the%20company%20Epic%20Games%3F",
     correct_answer: "Unreal",
     incorrect_answers: ["Unity", "Game%20Maker%3A%20Studio", "Cry%20Engine"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "If%20a%20%22360%20no-scope%22%20is%20one%20full%20rotation%20before%20shooting%2C%20how%20many%20rotations%20would%20a%20%221080%20no-scope%22%20be%3F",
     correct_answer: "3",
     incorrect_answers: ["4", "2", "5"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20these%20levels%20does%20NOT%20appear%20in%20the%20console%2FPC%20versions%20of%20the%20game%20%22Sonic%20Generations%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "Mushroom%20Hill",
     incorrect_answers: ["City%20Escape", "Planet%20Wisp", "Sky%20Sanctuary"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20was%20the%20first%20video%20game%20in%20the%20Batman%20%22Arkham%22%20series%3F",
     correct_answer: "Arkham%20Asylum",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Arkham%20Knight",
       "Arkham%20City",
       "Arkham%20Origins",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20does%20IWHBYD%20stand%20for%20on%20the%20skull%20in%20the%20Halo%20series%3F",
     correct_answer: "I%20Would%20Have%20Been%20Your%20Daddy",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "I%20Wanna%20Have%20Babies%20You%20Down",
       "I%20Would%20Hate%20Being%20Your%20Driver",
       "I%20Would%20Have%20Bought%20Your%20Dog",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20%22Worms%22%20series%20of%20video%20games%2C%20which%20of%20these%20weapons%20is%20affected%20by%20wind%3F",
     correct_answer: "Bazooka",
     incorrect_answers: ["Grenade", "Air%20Strike", "Mortar"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20most%20FPS%20video%20games%20such%20as%20Counter-Strike%2C%20shooting%20which%20part%20of%20the%20body%20does%20the%20highest%20damage%3F",
     correct_answer: "Head",
     incorrect_answers: ["Arm", "Leg", "Chest"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20Portal%202%2C%20how%20did%20CEO%20of%20Aperture%20Science%2C%20Cave%20Johnson%2C%20presumably%20die%3F",
     correct_answer: "Moon%20Rock%20Poisoning",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Accidentally%20sending%20a%20portal%20to%20the%20Moon",
       "Slipped%20in%20the%20shower",
       "Asbestos%20Poisoning",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20Mario%20spin-off%20game%20did%20Waluigi%20make%20his%20debut%3F",
     correct_answer: "Mario%20Tennis",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Mario%20Party%203",
       "Mario%20Kart%3A%20Double%20Dash%21%21",
       "Mario%20Golf%3A%20Toadstool%20Tour",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20Super%20Smash%20Bros.%20Series%3F",
     correct_answer: "Masahiro%20Sakurai",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Reggie%20Fils-Aim%C3%A9",
       "Bill%20Trinen",
       "Hideo%20Kojima",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "Who%20created%20the%202011%20Video%20Game%20%22Minecraft%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "Markus%20Persson",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Jens%20Bergensten",
       "Daniel%20Rosenfeld",
       "Carl%20Manneh",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "TF2%3A%20What%20code%20does%20Soldier%20put%20into%20the%20door%20keypad%20in%20%22Meet%20the%20Spy%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "1111",
     incorrect_answers: ["1432", "1337", "No%20code"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20was%20Frank%20West%27s%20job%20in%20%22Dead%20Rising%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "Photojournalist",
     incorrect_answers: ["Janitor", "Chef", "Taxi%20Driver"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20PROTOTYPE%202.%20who%20is%20referred%20to%20as%20%22Tango%20Primary%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "James%20Heller",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Alex%20Mercer",
       "Dana%20Mercer",
       "Any%20Goliaths%20roaming%20around",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "How%20many%20differently%20shaped%20Tetris%20pieces%20are%20there%3F",
     correct_answer: "7",
     incorrect_answers: ["5", "6", "8"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20video%20game%20sparked%20controversy%20because%20of%20its%20hidden%20%22Hot%20Coffee%22%20minigame%3F",
     correct_answer: "Grand%20Theft%20Auto%3A%20San%20Andreas",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Grand%20Theft%20Auto%3A%20Vice%20City",
       "Hitman%3A%20Blood%20Money",
       "Cooking%20Mama",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "The%20starting%20pistol%20of%20the%20Terrorist%20team%20in%20a%20competitive%20match%20of%20Counter%20Strike%3A%20Global%20Offensive%20is%20what%3F",
     correct_answer: "Glock-18",
     incorrect_answers: ["Tec-9", "Desert%20Eagle", "Dual%20Berretas"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20game%20Battleblock%20Theater%2C%20what%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20voice%20actor%20who%20voiced%20the%20narrator%3F",
     correct_answer: "Will%20Stamper",
     incorrect_answers: ["Steve%20Blum", "Richard%20Epcar", "Yuri%20Lowenthal"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20what%20year%20was%20the%20first%20%22Mass%20Effect%22%20game%20released%3F",
     correct_answer: "2007",
     incorrect_answers: ["2008", "2009", "2010"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Who%20turns%20out%20to%20be%20the%20true%20victor%20in%20the%20Battle%20of%20Armageddon%20in%20Mortal%20Kombat%3F",
     correct_answer: "Shao%20Kahn",
     incorrect_answers: ["Liu%20Kang", "Shang%20Tsung", "Raiden"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20minimum%20level%20in%20the%20Defence%20skill%20is%20needed%20to%20equip%20Dragon%20Armour%20in%20the%20MMO%20RuneScape%3F",
     correct_answer: "60",
     incorrect_answers: ["65", "55", "70"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "When%20was%20Left%204%20Dead%202%20released%3F",
     correct_answer: "November%2017%2C%202009",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "May%203%2C%202008",
       "November%2030%2C%202009",
       "June%2030%2C%202010",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20year%20was%20Super%20Mario%20Bros.%20released%3F",
     correct_answer: "1985",
     incorrect_answers: ["1983", "1987", "1986"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "%22The%20Potato%20Sack%22%20was%20a%20collection%20of%20indie%20games%20released%20on%20Steam%20in%202011%20as%20a%20promotion%20for%20which%20game%3F",
     correct_answer: "Portal%202",
     incorrect_answers: ["Left%204%20Dead%202", "Half-Life%203", "Dota%202"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20%22Fallout%3A%20New%20Vegas%22%20quest%20is%20NOT%20named%20after%20a%20real-life%20song%3F",
     correct_answer: "They%20Went%20That-a-Way",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Come%20Fly%20With%20Me",
       "Ain%27t%20That%20a%20Kick%20in%20the%20Head",
       "Ring-a-Ding%20Ding",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20household%20item%20make%20the%20characters%20of%20%22Steins%3B%20Gate%22%20travel%20through%20time%3F",
     correct_answer: "Microwave",
     incorrect_answers: ["Computer", "Refrigerator", "Televison"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20Kirby%20game%20first%20introduced%20Copy%20Abilities%3F",
     correct_answer: "Kirby%27s%20Adventure",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Kirby%20Super%20Star",
       "Kirby%27s%20Dream%20Land%202",
       "Kirby%27s%20Dream%20Land",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20game%20%22Hearthstone%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20best%20rank%20possible%3F",
     correct_answer: "Rank%201%20Legend",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Rank%201%20Elite",
       "Rank%201%20Master",
       "Rank%201%20Supreme",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Who%20is%20the%20main%20protagonist%20in%20Danganronpa%202%3A%20Goodbye%20Despair%3F",
     correct_answer: "Hajime%20Hinata",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Nagito%20Komaeda",
       "Makoto%20Naegi",
       "Junko%20Enoshima",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20game%20was%20used%20to%20advertise%20Steam%3F",
     correct_answer: "Counter-Strike%201.6",
     incorrect_answers: ["Half-Life", "Half-Life%202", "Team%20Fortress"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20%22Overwatch%22%2C%20which%20hero%20is%20able%20to%20wallride%3F",
     correct_answer: "Lucio",
     incorrect_answers: ["Reinhardt", "Sombra", "Mercy"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20%22Call%20Of%20Duty%3A%20Zombies%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20machine%20that%20upgrades%20weapons%3F",
     correct_answer: "Pack-A-Punch",
     incorrect_answers: ["Wunderfizz", "Gersch%20Device", "Mule%20Kick"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "Who%20created%20the%20%22Metal%20Gear%22%20Series%3F",
     correct_answer: "Hideo%20Kojima",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Hiroshi%20Yamauchi",
       "Shigeru%20Miyamoto",
       "Gunpei%20Yokoi",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20last%20name%20of%20the%20primary%20female%20protagonist%20of%20Final%20Fantasy%20VIII%3F",
     correct_answer: "Heartilly",
     incorrect_answers: ["Loire", "Almasy", "Trepe"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20CoD%3A%20Black%20Ops%20III%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20rogue%20A.I.%20antagonist%3F",
     correct_answer: "Corvus",
     incorrect_answers: ["Cabal", "Legion", "Icarus"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20Pok%C3%A9mon%20can%20learn%20the%20move%20%22Secret%20Power%22%20by%20leveling%20up%3F",
     correct_answer: "Audino",
     incorrect_answers: ["Type%3ANull", "Arceus", "Silvally"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20games%20has%20the%20largest%20map%20size%3F",
     correct_answer: "Just%20Cause%202",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Grand%20Theft%20Auto%205",
       "The%20Elder%20Scrolls%204%3A%20%20Oblivion",
       "The%20Witcher%203%3A%20%20Wild%20Hunt",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20weapons%20in%20%22Counter-Strike%3A%20Global%20Offensive%22%20does%20not%20have%20a%20right-click%20function%3F",
     correct_answer: "XM1014",
     incorrect_answers: ["SG553", "R8%20Revolver", "USP-S"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20Pokemon%2C%20the%20ability%20Wonder%20Guard%20is%20exclusive%20to%20which%20Pokemon%3F%20",
     correct_answer: "Shedinja%20",
     incorrect_answers: ["Sableye", "Spiritomb", "Silvally%20"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Zelda%20games%20did%20not%20feature%20Ganon%20as%20a%20final%20boss%3F",
     correct_answer: "Majora%27s%20Mask",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Ocarina%20of%20Time",
       "Skyward%20Sword",
       "Breath%20of%20the%20Wild",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%202%20Valve%20Games%20are%20set%20in%20the%20same%20universe%3F",
     correct_answer: "Half-life%20and%20Portal",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Portal%20and%20Left%204%20Dead",
       "Half-life%20and%20Left%204%20Dead",
       "Half-life%20and%20Counter%20Strike",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20canceled%20projected%20by%20Blizzard%20Entertainment%20that%20would%20be%20later%20become%20Overwatch%3F",
     correct_answer: "Titan",
     incorrect_answers: ["Omnic", "Omega", "Ghost"],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20Splatoon%202%2C%20who%20are%20the%20members%20of%20Off%20The%20Hook%3F",
     correct_answer: "Pearl%20%26%20Marina",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Callie%20%26%20Marie",
       "Diamond%20%26%20Aquamarina",
       "DJ%20Octavio%20%26%20Crusty%20Sean",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20psychopath%28s%29%20in%20Dead%20Rising%201%20gave%20you%20the%20small%20chainsaw%3F",
     correct_answer: "Adam%20the%20Clown",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Cliff%20Hudson",
       "The%20convicts",
       "Larry%20the%20butcher",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "In%20the%20video%20game%20franchise%20%22Halo%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20UNSC%27s%20main%20opposing%20faction%20called%3F",
     correct_answer: "The%20Covenant",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "The%20Reckoning",
       "The%20Peoples",
       "The%20Slaughterers",
     ],
   },
 ];